alvinalexander.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy | alvinalexander.com

By Alvin Alexander. Last updated: January 9 2013

Alvin Alexander and alvinalexander.com do not attempt to track you in any way, shape, or form. In general we're just glad you came to visit, and hope you'll come back again.

That being said, this site currently uses the Drupal CMS, and if it stores any cookies to function properly, we never look at those. (I don't think it does, because you're all considered "anonymous users", but I could be wrong.) If you make comments on this website and supply your email address when leaving a comment, that email address is stored in a database table, but we don't use it for any purpose other than to let Drupal tell you that new comments have been posted related to what you wrote about, and even there you have to opt-in to even receive those (and you can also opt-out after the initial opt-in).

If you sign up for our mailing list, we use that list to tell people about website updates, and also to let them know if they've won a prize in one of our contests.

Now, beyond what we "track", which is basically the nothingness described above, there there are two caveats we need to share here.

##  Caveat 1: Google Analytics

The first caveat to share is that we do use Google Analytics to understand general aggregate traffic flow, particularly which pages are most popular. If you can imagine our situation, if we're writing about certain topics and nobody cares to read those topics, well, we're wasting our time, and that's something of interest to us, so we use Google Analytics as a tool there.

##  Caveat 2: Advertisers

The second caveat is that we work with other companies to put advertisements on this website, including Google, ValueClick, and ThinkGeek. Here's what we know about their privacy policies.

###  Google Adsense

As far as I can tell, Google has a [general privacy statement](http://www.google.com/privacy.html), and a second [advertising privacy statement](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Both of those pages are much longer than I care to include here, so please read their statements to learn about Google's privacy policies.

###  ValueClick

I don't use ValueClick for ads much any more, but as near as I can tell, this next link will take you to the [ValueClick privacy policy](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/about/privacy/display-web-user).

ValueClick was also nice enough to send me an email to let me know that a change in our contract requires me to update this page, and they've provided the following pre-written verbiage that relates specifically to their advertismenets shown on the devdaily.com website:

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

###  ThinkGeek

Here's a link to the [ThinkGeek privacy policy](http://www.thinkgeek.com/privacy.shtml). Again it's too long to reprint here in its entirety, so I recommend reading the policy on their website, which should also always be up to date.
